A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Scientific Staff Biographical Files FA260
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Harris, Stanton A., 1931-1935 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Hartman, Thomas L., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Hartmann, Guido, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Hastings, Albert Baird, 1921-1925, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Haugaard, H.C. Gotfred, 1939-1944 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Hausheer, Walter C., 1926-1928 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Hausmann, Werner, 1948-1956 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Havens, Walter P., 1940-1944 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Hawkins, James A., 1922-1930 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Hayes, J. J., 1939 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Heggie, Robert M., 1938-1939 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Heimrod, George W., 1907-1923 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Heimrod, George W., 1907-1923 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Heimrod, George W., 1907-1923 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Heinze, Kurt, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Helmer, Oscar M., 1927-1931 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Hendricks, Sterling B., 1926-1938 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Henneman, Elwood, 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Hercik, Ferdinand, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Heremans, Joseph F., 1959 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Hetler, Donald McKinley, 1926-1927 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Heymann, Karl, 1930, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Hiatt, Caspar W., III, 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Hildebrand, Earl Martin, 1939, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Hill, Douglas William, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Hill, Edgar S., 1931 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Hill, Samuel E., 1929, 1938-1941 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Hilleman, Maurice R., 1951 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Hiller, Alma, 1935-1958 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Hintzsche, G. W. Erich, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Hirst, George K., 1935-1939, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Hitchcock, Charles H., 1925-1926, 1934, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Hitchcock, David, 1921-1926 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Hobson, Derek, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Hodes, Horace L., 1936, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Hodge, Benjamin E., 1930 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Hodgkin, Alan L., 1937 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Hoffman, Donald C., 1928-1930 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Hoffmann, Alexander, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Hofmann, Klaus, 1937-1947 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Hogeboom, George H., 1940-1957 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Holden, Raymond F., Jr., 1934 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Holman, Delavan V., 1934 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Holman, Halsted R., 1955-1960 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Holter, Heinz D., 1934, 1950, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Holzer, Franz J., 1933-1934 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Hope, Dorothea Stater, 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Horvath, Arthemy A., 1927-1930 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Horvath, Arthemy A., 1927-1930 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Horvath, Arthemy A., 1927-1930 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Howard, Charles W., 1911-1912 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Howard, Marion E., 1927, 1930, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Howe, Paul E., 1916-1919, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Hu, Ch'uan-k'uei, 1932-1933 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Huang, Chen-hsiang, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Hudack, Stephen S., 1930-1931, 1942, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Huebner, Charles F., 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hughes, Thomas P., 1926 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Hülsmann, Willem C., 1959 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Hummel, L. Edgar, 1934-1944 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Hunt, Carlton, C., 1952-1955 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Hursh, John B., 1937 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Hurst, E. Weston, 1932-1933 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Hurst, E. Weston, 1932-1933 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Hurst, E. Weston, 1932-1933 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Huseby, Robert A., 1944 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Hussey, Raymond, 1919-1922, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Ing, Harry Raymond, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Ingebrigsten, Ragnvald, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Ingram, Vernon M., 1950 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Ingvaldsen, Thorsten, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Insull, William, Jr., 1952-1959 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Irons, Vernal, 1932-1933 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Irving, George W., Jr., 1939-1945 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Irwin, Malcolm R., 1928-1930 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Isler, Otto, 1934-1936 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Itoh, Shinji, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Jackson, Sylvia Fitton, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Jacobs, John L., 1931-1934 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Jacobsen, C.F., 1947 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Jacques, Alfred G., 1926-1934, 1939-1941 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Jacques, Alfred G., 1926-1934, 1939-1941 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Jacquez, John A., 1947-1948 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Jailer, Joseph W., 1941-1945 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- James, Anthony T., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Jamieson, Ross A., 1914-1916 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Jeanrenaud, Bernard, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Jensen, James H., 1931-1935 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Jobling, James W., 1906-1910, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Johnson, Charles W., 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Johnson, Folke, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Johnston, Christopher, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Jones, Frederick S., 1913-1937 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Jones, Frederick S., 1913-1937 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Jones, Frederick S., 1913-1937 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Jones, Frederick S., 1913-1937 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Jones, Frederick S., 1913-1937 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Jorpes, Erik, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Joseph, Don R., 1907-1912 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Joyner, Austin L., 1935-1936, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Julianelle, Louis A., 1924-1930, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Kaje, Akira, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Kallman, Frances L., 1951 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Kamerling, Samuel E., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Kao, Chien-yuan, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Kaufman, Edwin H., 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Kavanau, Lee, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Kay, Robert Lee, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Keegan, John Jay, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Kelley, William H., 1929 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Kelman, Arthur, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Kemp, Norman E., 1958 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Kerman, Roderick Patrick, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Khalifa, Ismail Abu Bakr, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Kidd, John G., 1934-1958 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Kilbourne, Edwin D., 1947-1954 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Kimmelman, Leonard J., 1955 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- King, Lester S., 1936-1943 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- King, Robert C., 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Kingsland, Lawrence C., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Kirk, Esben, 1931-1933 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Kleiner, Israel S., 1910-1933 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Kliger, Israel J., 1916-1958 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Kline, Benjamin S., 1912-1915 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Knight, Claude A., Jr., 1940-1948 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Knutti, Ralph E., 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Komatsu, Shigeru, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Korb, Charles, 1923-1927 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Krakaur, Richard B., 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Krampitz, Lester Orville, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Kreider, Leonard C., 1936-1937 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Kreitlow, Kermit William, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Krueger, Albert P., 1929-1933, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Kubie, Lawrence S., 1925-1930 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Kugell, Victor H., 1932 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Kuhns, William J., 1951-1953 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Kurnick, Nathaniel B., 1947-1954 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Kuttner, Ann G., 1924-1949 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Labby, Daniel H., 1945-1946 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Lacaillade, Charles William, Jr., 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Lack, Charles H., 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Lacorte, José, 1944-1946 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Lafontaine, Jean-Gabriel, 1956-1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Lahelle, Oskar H., 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Lamar, Richard V., 1907-1912 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Lange, Fritz, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Lange, Linda B., 1912 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Lansing, Albert I., 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Laporte, Yves F., 1946-1952 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Lappano, Eleanor R., 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Larramendi, Luis M.H., 1954-1958 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Larson, Henry M., 1916-1917 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Laskaris, Thomas, 1941-1946 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Lauffer, Max A., Jr., 1937-1948 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Lauson, Henry D., 1946-1950 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Lavin, George I., 1932-1956 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Lavin, George I., 1932-1956 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Lawson, Mary Rowley, 1911-1920 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- LeBlanc, Thomas J., 1920 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- [not assigned] (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Lehman, Jörgen Erik, 1935, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Leigh, Frederick W., 1954 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Leiter, Louis, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Lemberger, Helene, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Leonis, José, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Levine, Philip, 1925-1956 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Levinson, Solomon, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Levy, Robert L., 1919-1922 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Lewis, William Hall, Jr., 1931-1951 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Lieberman, Moses, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Lieberman, Shulamite Ben-Harel, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Light, Jacob, 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Lin, Mei, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Linder, Geoffry C., 1921-1924 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Lindstedt, Sven, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Linton, Richard W., 1927 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Little, Ralph B., 1914-1955 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Little, Ralph B., 1914-1955 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Little, Ralph B., 1914-1955 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Little, Ralph B., 1914-1955 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Little, Ralph B., 1914-1955 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Liu, Jui-Heng, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Liu, Shih-Hao, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Long, John G., 1918 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Long, Perrin H., 1926-1954 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Loomis, Dorothy, 1923, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- López-Suárez, Juan, 1916-1917, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Loring, Hubert S., 1935 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Lowenhaupt, Benjamin, 1957-1960 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Lucas, James Robert, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Lundberg, Anders, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Lundsgaard, Christen, 1915-1930 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Luyet, Basile, 1930-1941 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Lynch, Clara Julia, 1918-1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- McCarthy, Earl F., 1937-1940 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- McCartney, James E., 1922-1925, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 3A)
- McCrudden, Francis H., 1905-1912 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- McDonald, Margaret, 1940-1943 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- McEwen, Currier, 1928-1938, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- MacFadyen, Douglas A., 1931-1948 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- MacFadyen, Douglas A., 1931-1948 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Macfarlane, Angus, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- McGhee, R. Barclay, 1948-1954 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Machado, Raul D., 1958-1960 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Macht, David I., 1923-1924 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- McIntosh, John F., 1923-1928 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- McIntyre, Archibald K., 1946-1953 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Mackaness, George B., 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- MacKay, Eaton M., 1925-1928, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Mackenzie, Ian, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Mackenzie, Ronald D., 1926 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- McLean, Franklin C., 1914-1928 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- MacLeod, Archibald Garrard, 1932-1934 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- MacLeod, Colin Munro, 1933-1948, 1954, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- McMurray, Virginia M., 1954, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- MacNamara, Jean, 1930-1933 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- McNew, George L., 1935-1939, 1949, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- MacNider, William de B., 1916-1929, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- MacNider, William de B., 1916-1929, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- MacPherson, Daniel A., 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- [not assigned] (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Magill, Thomas P., 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Maisin, Joseph H., 1922 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Majno, Guido, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Malkiel, Saul, 1945-1957 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Mall, Franklin P., 1913 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Malm, Ole Jacob Worm-Müller, 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Manwaring, Wilfred H., 1905-1916 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Manwaring, Wilfred H., 1905-1916 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Manwaring, Wilfred H., 1905-1916 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Manwaring, Wilfred H., 1905-1916 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Manwaring, Wilfred H., 1905-1916 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Marchand, Werner (and family), 1915-1953 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Marchand, Werner (and family), 1915-1953 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Marfey, S. Peter, 1956-1959 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Mark, Donald D., 1955-1957 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Marker, Russell Earl, 1928-1934 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Marmur, Julius, 1952-1954 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Marrazzi, Amedeo S., 1942 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Marshak, Alfred G., 1945-1947 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Martin, Samuel P., 1948-1954 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Martinaglia, Giovanni, 1920 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Martinovitch, Petar N., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Mashima, Hidenobu, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Matoltsy, Alexander Gedeon, 1956-1959 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Matsuo, Iwao, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Matsushita, Hiroshi, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Maurer, Fred F., 1947-1948 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Medawar, P.B, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Medigreceanu, Florentin (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Mehltretter, Charles L., 1936 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Merrill, Malcolm H., 1931-1936 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Meyer, Arthur Louis, 1914-1924 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Meyer, Gustave M., 1908-1945 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Meyer, Jean-Paul, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Meyer, Willy, 1908-1915, 1923, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Meyer, Willy, 1908-1915, 1923, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Mezera, Raymond A., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Middlebrook, Gardner, 1945-1958 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Mikeska, Louis Alois, 1920-1930 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Miller, Benjamin, F., 1933-1936 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Miller, C. Philip, 1920, 1926, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Miller, David K., 1931, 1936-1937, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Miller, Frederick R., 1929-1939 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Miller, Gail L., 1934-1952 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Miller, Mary L., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Milstone, J. Haskell, 1940-1941 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Mirick, George S., 1938-1946 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Mitra, Sandhya, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Moen, Johannes K., 1932 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Mogabgab, William J., 1950-1956 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Moller, Eggert Hugo Heiberg, 1925-1928 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Monroy, Alberto, 1949-1952 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Monroy, Anna, 1949-1950 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Montgomery, O. F., 1916 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Moore, Henry F., 1914-1917 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Moore, Joseph Earle, 1921, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Moore, Norman S., 1928 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Moore, Richmond L., 1925 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Morágues-Gonzalez, Vicens, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Morgan, Hugh J., 1921-1924 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Morgan, Isabel M., 1938-1944 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Morison, Rufus A., 1916-1918 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Morton, John J., 1914-1916 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Moscona, Aron Arthur, 1955-1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Moses, Montrose J., 1954-1959 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Muckenfuss, Ralph Stewart, 1925-1953 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Mudd, Stuart, 1923-1946 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Mueller, Conrad George, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Mueller, Paul, 1952-1954 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Mueller, Henry R., 1927-1929 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- [not assigned] (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Murphy, George E., 1954 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Murphy, Leslie C., 1949-1950 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Murray, Cecil D., 1923 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Murray, Henry A., Jr., 1922-1925 (Box 23, Folder 11A)
- Murray, John W., 1934, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Muskat, Irving E., 1933-1934 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Muus, Jytte Marie, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Mycek, Mary J., 1955-1956 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Nagy, Bela F., 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Nai, Dino, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Nakahara, Waro, 1918-1925, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Nassar, Yolanda Hamuy, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Nemes, Marjorie M., 1955-1958 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Neumann, Charles G., 1949 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Newton, Alison Anne, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Nicholson, Frederick Max, 1921-1924, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Niemann, Carl G., 1935-1937 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Nigg, Clara, 1929-1947 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Norberg, Bo M.F., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Norman, Philip S., 1954-1955 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Norval, Ian P., 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Novy, F.G., 1905-1912 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Ocfemia, Gerardo O., 1954 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Odoriz, Jose B., 1935-1941 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Ohira, Tockzo, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Okkels, Harald, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Oliver, Jean, 1916-1919, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Olivo, Oliviero, 1928-1929 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Orcutt, Marion L., 1931-1935 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Osborn, Herbert T., 1932 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Oster, Gerald, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Osterhout, Suydam, 1955-1956 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Ovakimian, Gaik, 1937, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Overman, John, 1953-1957 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Page, Irvine H., 1930-1942 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Palacios, Raul, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Paladini, Alejandro C., 1950-1952 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Palay, Sanford L., 1947-1952 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Palmer, Walter W. (Box 24, Folder 11A)
- Paoletti, Caris, 1949-1951 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Pappas, George D., 1952-1954 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Parker, Raymond C., 1939 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Parker, Robert F., 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Parsons, Robert J., 1935-1937, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Patterson, Arthur Lindo, 1929-1931 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Peachey, Lee D., 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Pearce, John M., 1936-1937 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Pearcy, James F., 1928 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Peck, Harry D., Jr., 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Pelluet, Dixie, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Perlman, Ely, 1942-1946 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Perlman, Ely, 1942-1946 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Perlzweig, William A., 1916 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Peters, John P., 1955 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Pfaltz, Mimosa H. (Mrs. Paul D. Fejos), 1922-1956 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Philips, Robert A., 1940-1944 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Pirie, N.W., 1935-1936 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Pittman, Margaret (Jane), 1930 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Plantenga, Herma, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Pollock, Heinz W., 1937 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Powell, Eugene V., 1920 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Pray, Alfred R., 1954-1957 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Presland, John Richard, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Price, William Conway, 1932-1958 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Price, Winston H., 1946-1954 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Pringle, Anna Ludutsky, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Pritchett, Ida W., 1916-1929 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Rabinowitz, Murray, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Rake, Geoffrey W., 1930-1940 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Rall, Wilfrid, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Ramos, Juan Garcia, 1948-1949 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Rasek, J.M., 1930 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Rathgeb, Paul, 1950-1951 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Ray, Roger B., 1944-1947 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Raychaudhuri, Syamaprasad, 1947-1952 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Raymond, Albert L., 1926-1940 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Redden, William R., 1916-1917 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Reeves, Richard E., 1937, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Reichert, Philip, 1924-1926, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Reimann, Hobart A., 1923-1926, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Reis, Jose, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Renshaw, Birdsey, 1938-1942 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Reverberi, Guiseppe, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Rhoads, Cornelius P., 1928-1959 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Rhoads, Cornelius P., 1928-1959 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Rhoads, Cornelius P., 1928-1959 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Rhoads, Cornelius P., 1928-1959 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Rhoads, Cornelius P., 1928-1959 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Rhoads, Cornelius P., 1928-1959 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Rich, Clayton, 1950-1960 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Richards, William T., 1936-1953 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Richter, Goetz, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Rieben, Willi K., 1941-1943 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Riggs, Lorrin A., 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Ris, Hans, 1944-1948 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Ritts, Roy Eliot, Jr., 1955-1958 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Robbins, Elliott W., 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Robbins, Frederick C., 1949, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Robbins, Phillips W., 1960 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Robertson, Oswald H., 1915-1920 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Robinson, Eugene Sant, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Robinson, Frank H., Jr., 1937-1939 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Robinson, George Canby, 1910-1925 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Robson, William, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Rocha e Silva, M., 1941 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Rogers, David E., 1954 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Rogers, Edward S., 1932 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Rogers, Stanfield, 1947-1949, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Rolf, Ida P., 1921-1926, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Roof, Betty Sams, 1948-1959 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Rosahn, Paul D., 1930-1937 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Rosen, Sidney, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Rosenbaum, Robert M., 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Rosenbusch, Carlos T., 1937 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Ross, A. Frank, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Ross, William Fenton, 1934-1943 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Rothbard, Mary B., 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Rothbard, Sidney, 1940-1954 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Rudomin, Pedro Naum, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Rule, Leroy Colter, 1942-1943 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Runnström, John, 1933, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Rzucidio, Ludwik, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Saddington, Ronald S., 1930-1933 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Saddington, Ronald S., 1930-1933 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Saddington, Ronald S., 1930-1933 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Saddington, Ronald S., 1930-1933 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Saddington, Ronald S., 1930-1933 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Saddington, Ronald S., 1930-1933 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Saddington, Ronald S., 1930-1933 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Saenz, Arturo, 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Saetren, Hans T., 1950-1951 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Sager, Ruth, 1949-1955 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Sakai, Toshio, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Sakimura, Kanjyo, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Salomon, Kurt, 1929-1931 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Salvesen, Harald A., 1919, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Sanderson, Everett S., 1923, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Santesson, Lars, 1929-1931 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Sarles, Merritt P., 1929-1934 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Sato, Yoshio, 1946-1951 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Sauvé, Gaston, 1951-1955 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Saxton, John A., Jr., 1935-1936 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Saz, Arthur K., 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Schachman, Howard, 1942-1948 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Schaefer, Werner B., 1950, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Scharrer, Ernst & Berta, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Scharrer, Ernst & Berta, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Scherer, William F., 1954 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Scherp, Henry W., 1931-1934 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Schlesinger, Robert W., 1940-1954, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Schmidt, Gerhard, 1937-1959, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Schneider, Walter C., 1946-1948 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Schober, Bruno, 1946-1949 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Schoenheyder, Fritz E.H., 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Schormueller, Anton, 1931-1935 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Schott, Ralph G., 1931-1932 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Schroeder, Henry A., 1935-1949 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Schubert, Maxwell P., 1929-1940 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Schultz, Mark P., 1929-1936, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Schwartz, Irving L., 1950-1958 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Schwarzenbach, Gerold K., 1937, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Schwentker, Francis F., 1930-1942 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Scott, Albert B., 1929, 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Scott, Gordon H., 1927-1928 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Scott, Thomas F. McNair, 1934, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Scudder, John, 1938-1941 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Seastone, Charles V., 1934-1947 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Sebrell, W. Henry, Jr., 1955-1958 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Sedar, Albert W., 1953-1954 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Seelig, S.F., 1931-1932 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Siefried, Oskar, 1928-1932 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Seilern-Aspang, Friedrich, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Sendroy, Julius, 1920-1949 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Senior, James K., 1914-1922 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Shamoff, Vladimir N., 1913 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Shank, Robert E., 1940-1946 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Shaw, Elliott N., 1948-1956 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Sia, Richard Ho-Ping, 1922-1923 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Sigurdsson, Björn, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Sigurgeirsson, Thorbjorn, 1945-1947 (Box 28, Folder 14)